<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-08-29T21:42:35-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Rob Dudley - Writing’s about business, technology, and design.</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Feedback From my Tesla Innovation Project Teammates</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/school/2021/08/27/feedback-from-my-tesla-innovation-project-teammates.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Feedback From my Tesla Innovation Project Teammates" /><published>2021-08-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-08-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/school/2021/08/27/feedback-from-my-tesla-innovation-project-teammates</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/school/2021/08/27/feedback-from-my-tesla-innovation-project-teammates.html">&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;/tesla-innovation-project&quot;&gt;Tesla innovation project&lt;/a&gt; was the capstone project for my Corporate Entrepreneurship class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the semester, each of us had to give feedback to the other team members related to their work ethic and overall involvement in the project. We also had 100 points to award each member, but you could give someone more than 100. However, if you gave someone more than 100, say 110, you had to take the extra 10 points away from someone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I received the following grades from my peers:  100, 102, 115, and 130 for an average of 111.75.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what they said about me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I appreciated Robert for being the person keeping the team on track and reminding us when to turn everything in. He was also the one to create the member’s concept illustrations, which he didn’t have to but still offered. Robert organized all of our research concepts and did more than he was suppose to, which really helped our team finish everything on time.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Robert, It was a pleasure working with you on this project. You went above and beyond throughout the project and kept us on track. Good luck in your future endeavors!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You were instrumental in the completion of our project and I really appreciate all of the work and effort you put into getting it done. Our project would not have been completed to the standard that it was had you not been a member of our team. Thank you for your work and commitment.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Thank you for being a critical part of our project! Your efforts were integral to providing a focus that allowed us as a team to perfect our ideas and thoughts into something meaningful. You are a great organizer, leader, and teammate and I’m glad to have spent the last month working with you!”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="school" /><summary type="html">The Tesla innovation project was the capstone project for my Corporate Entrepreneurship class.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">‘Howdy, world!’</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/business/2021/07/16/howdy-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="‘Howdy, world!’" /><published>2021-07-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-07-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/business/2021/07/16/howdy-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/business/2021/07/16/howdy-world.html">&lt;p&gt;/business/2021/07/16/howdy-world.html &lt;br /&gt;
‘Howdy, world!’ &lt;br /&gt;
http://localhost:4000 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my first blog post! I suppose I should start with the reason for this site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started this project to work on my writing, showcase various projects I’ve done, and as
an exercise of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://fs.blog/2021/02/feynman-learning-technique/&quot;&gt;Feynman technique of learning&lt;/a&gt; (i.e., writing about things you wish to understand more).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also hoping this site will help me stand out among my peers once I graduate in December 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="business" /><summary type="html">/business/2021/07/16/howdy-world.html ‘Howdy, world!’ http://localhost:4000</summary></entry></feed>